<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Brandon Rajkumar</title>
        <link>https://Brajkumar1992.github.io</link>
        <description>A outline of my professional career.</description>
        <generator>Zola</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <atom:link href="https://Brajkumar1992.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title>MPHil Physics (Solar Astronomy)</title>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <link>https://Brajkumar1992.github.io/Education/mphil/</link>
            <guid>https://Brajkumar1992.github.io/Education/mphil/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;AR1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Active Region&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2016-2021   &lt;em&gt;The University of the West Indies&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;   St. Augustine&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MPhil. Physics (Focus - Solar Astronomy): Awarded with High Commendation&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thesis Title:&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; A Fractal Analysis of Umbrae, Penumbrae and Magnetograms within Active Regions.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; The scale free fractal dimensions were determined for the umbral and penumbral regions as well as the underlying magnetic field regions of 16 active regions observed between June-November 2015. Hi-resolution white light images were obtained from the University College of the Cayman Islands (UCCI) Observatory on the Grand Cayman while magnetograms were obtained from the Joint Science Operations Centre (JSOC). The area-perimeter method was used, and the fractal dimensions of umbral and penumbral regions were found to be 2.09 ± 0.42 and 1.72 ± 0.4 respectively with strong and weak magnetic field groups having fractal dimensions of 1.79 ± 0.49 and 1.96 ± 0.29 respectively. Using the fractal dimensions as an indicator for complexity, it was observed that complex, weak magnetic fields produce less complex penumbral regions while less complex, strong magnetic fields produce more complex umbral regions. This observation supports the recent model of sunspot formation where strong magnetic fields are trapped within the umbra reducing their freedom of motion indicated by the lower fractal dimension while unbound, weak magnetic fields found in penumbral regions are indicated by higher fractal dimensions. However, the reduced temperature caused by trapping of the strong magnetic fields in the umbral regions lead to more complex umbral structures while higher temperatures in penumbral regions form less complex penumbral structures as indicated by the respective fractal dimensions. An initial temporal analysis of the umbral and penumbral structures’ reveals a correlation which indicates that the changes in complexity between regions may be linked.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Tteokbokki</title>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <link>https://Brajkumar1992.github.io/Food/tteokbokki/</link>
            <guid>https://Brajkumar1992.github.io/Food/tteokbokki/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;tteokbokki.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LX 200&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Korean inspired Tteokbokki&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ingredients:&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;cylinder shaped rice cake&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;water&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;dried anchovies&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;dried kelp&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;hot pepper paste (gochujang)&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Korean hot pepper flakes (gochugaru)&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sugar&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;green onion&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fish cakes&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;hard boiled eggs (optional)&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Paella</title>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <link>https://Brajkumar1992.github.io/Food/paella/</link>
            <guid>https://Brajkumar1992.github.io/Food/paella/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;paella.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LX 200&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spanish inspired Paella&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ingredients:&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;olive oil&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;onion&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;hot smoked paprika &lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;dried thyme&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;paella or risotto rice&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;dry sherry or white wine&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;tomatoes&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;garlic&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chicken stock&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;seafood mix&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;lemon&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;parsley&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Doubles</title>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <link>https://Brajkumar1992.github.io/Food/doubles/</link>
            <guid>https://Brajkumar1992.github.io/Food/doubles/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;doubles.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LX 200&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Doubles&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ingredients:&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bara&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;flour&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;saffron powder (tumeric)&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;baking powder&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;yeast&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;brown sugar&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;salt&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;water&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;oil&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Channa&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;channa&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;water&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;baking soda&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;oil&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;curry&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;saffron (tumeric)&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;geera (cumin)&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;masala&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;garlic&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;onion&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chadon beni&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;salt and pepper&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Personification Series</title>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <link>https://Brajkumar1992.github.io/BRCreations/personification/</link>
            <guid>https://Brajkumar1992.github.io/BRCreations/personification/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;Sun.png&quot; alt=&quot;Sun&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet &lt;strong&gt;Eliane!&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; Personification of the Sun.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eliane has Hebrew&#x2F;Greek&#x2F;Latin origins and means &amp;quot;sun&amp;quot;. Seen here screaming becuse the Sun can sometimes be fierce. Her red hair and dark lips hint at her fiery persona. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;Mercury.png&quot; alt=&quot;Mercury&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet &lt;strong&gt;Malakai!&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; Personification of Mercury.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Malakai has Hebrew origins and means &amp;quot;my messenger&amp;quot;. Seen here as a wide-eyed kid eager to pass on messages and covered in dirt from running around. The dirt also hints at Mercury&#x27;s scared surface from its many asteroid impacts. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;Venus.png&quot; alt=&quot;Venus&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet &lt;strong&gt;Adonis!&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; Personification of Venus.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adonis has Latin&#x2F;Greek origins and means &amp;quot;very handsome young man&amp;quot;. The name is also that of a young man who entices Aphrodite in some Greek myths. Seen here with a sensual look in his eyes, his dark skin and dark orange eyes hint at the hot smoldering atmosphere of Venus. Often depicted as the goddess of love, here Venus is embodied by the namesake of one of the few men the goddess wants but cannot have according to lore. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;Earth.png&quot; alt=&quot;Earth&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet &lt;strong&gt;Terra!&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; Personification of Earth.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Terra has Latin&#x2F;Greek origins and means &amp;quot;land or territory&amp;quot;. The name was also used as the Roman goddess of the Earth.Seen here with thick green hair, complex with messy curls which represents the forests and plants of the Earth. Her dark skin hints at the rich soil beneath it all while her blue lips and eyes, along with her clothes imitate the vast oceans of the Earth.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;Moon.png&quot; alt=&quot;Moon&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet &lt;strong&gt;Luna!&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; Personification of the Moon.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Luna has Latin origins and means &amp;quot;Moon&amp;quot;. Her fair complexion hints at the bright full moon while her choppy violet hair represents the bright streaks around the moon&#x27;s craters.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;Mars.png&quot; alt=&quot;Mars&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet &lt;strong&gt;Russ!&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; Personification of Mars.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While Russ has Slavic origins and means &amp;quot;Redish blonde&amp;quot; it ws choosen as a play on rusty which describes the surface of the planet. Seen here with his rich rusty colored hair which hints at the planet&#x27;s iron rich surface while the messiness of his hair are hints to the strong winds on the planet. His intense gaze and dark eyes are homage to the planet&#x27;s depiction as the god of was in Greek and Roman mythology. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;Jupiter.png&quot; alt=&quot;Jupiter&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet &lt;strong&gt;Jeevana!&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; Personification of Jupiter.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jeevana has Hindu&#x2F;Indian&#x2F;Tamil&#x2F;Telugu origins and means &amp;quot;Life or Bringer of Life&amp;quot;. Her dark skin are representive of the dark colored atmosphere of Jupiter while her deep red lips representing the storms of Jupiter. The great red spot is represented by the dot on her forehead (called a bindi - it is traditionally worn by Hindu women to indicate that they are married. However in modern times it is also worn as fashion.)&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;Saturn.png&quot; alt=&quot;Saturn&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet &lt;strong&gt;Mira!&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; Personification of Saturn.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mira has varios origins and meetings. Here it was inspired by the Latin and Arabic origins which mean wonderful and princess respectively. Seen here with a head wrap which mimics the colors of Saturn&#x27;s surface along with her dark skin, lips and eyes. The giant hoop earrings she wears is a hint to the rings that surround Saturn.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;Uranus.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Uranus&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet &lt;strong&gt;William!&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; Personification of Uranus.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;William has Germanic origins and means &amp;quot;Resolute Protector&amp;quot;. However, the name was chosen in honor of the person who discovered the planet, Sir Willian Herchel. Seen here sporting a very disapproving look, William is tired of all the butt jokes. His aqua marine hair and beard are hints to the color of Uranus. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;Neptune.png&quot; alt=&quot;Neptune&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet &lt;strong&gt;Kailani!&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; Personification of Neptune.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kailani has Hawaiian origins and means &amp;quot;Sky and Sea&amp;quot;. Seen here with blue lips and hair which mimics the planet&#x27;s color while her messy hair hints at the strong winds of Neptune&#x27;s atmosphere. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;Pluto.png&quot; alt=&quot;Pluto&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet &lt;strong&gt;Persephone!&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; Personification of Pluto.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Persephone has pre-Greek origins and was the goddess of vegetation in Greek mythology. Here, my personification of Pluto embodies her name sake. Usually, the mythology of Persephone is that she was kidnapped and dragged by Hades (Pluto), god of the underworld into his domain. She is allowed to visit her moder for parts of the year and this is why we have seasons. However, in this depiction, Persephone was not kidnapped but  willing participant. Her fair skin and blonde hair shows her as the embodiment of spring and her ties to growth, harvest and beauty. As she accepts death and travels to the underworld with her lover, she dawns black lipstick and earrings. Her crown is made of boney claws and she adopts a stone cold glare knowing the power she has over her husband and his domain. However, her origins aren&#x27;t lost and even in her acceptance of the underworld, it shines through as shown by the dark but vivid purple flowers which adore her crown and hair sticks. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>A Fractal Analysis of Magnetograms Within Active Regions</title>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <link>https://Brajkumar1992.github.io/Publications/paper1/</link>
            <guid>https://Brajkumar1992.github.io/Publications/paper1/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;Rajkumar, Brandon, and Shirin Haque. 2020. &amp;quot;A Fractal Analysis of Magnetograms Within Active Regions.&amp;quot; Solar Physics 295 (2): 1-12. doi: 10.1007&#x2F;s11207-017-1184-2.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract -&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; The magnetograms of sixteen Active Regions, observed during June - November 2015, were obtained from the Joint Science Operations Center and used to determine the fractal dimensions of various magnetic field groups. The fields were divided into strong (positive and negative) and weak (positive and negative) groupings. The area-perimeter method was used to determine the fractal dimensions for the umbral and penumbral regions of the magnetograms. The fractal dimensions were found to be 1.79 ± 0.49 and 1.96 ± 0.29 for strong and weak magnetic fields respectively. When compared to the umbral and penumbral fractal dimensions determined by (Rajkumar, Haque and Hrudey, 2017) using white light images, an inverse relationship was found, with the umbra showing lower fractal dimensions than the penumbra for the magnetic field groups compared to the intensity images. This directly implies that there is greater complexity in the penumbral magnetic field groupings than the umbral region. This has implications for models that constrain how the magnetic field groups are contained in the cooler umbral regions.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;mag1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Magnetogram&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Fractal Dimensions of Umbral and Penumbral Regions of Sunspots.</title>
            <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <link>https://Brajkumar1992.github.io/Publications/paper2/</link>
            <guid>https://Brajkumar1992.github.io/Publications/paper2/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;Rajkumar, B, S Haque, and W Hrudey. 2017. &amp;quot;Fractal dimensions of umbral and penumbral regions of sunspots.&amp;quot; Solar Physics 292 (11): 1-16.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract -&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; The images of sunspots in sixteen active regions taken at the UCCI Observatory in Grand Cayman during June - November 2015, were used to determine their fractal dimensions using the perimeter-area method for the umbral and the penumbral region. Scale free fractal dimensions of 2.09 ± 0.42 and 1.72 ± 0.4 were found respectively. This value was higher than the value determined by Chumak and Chumak (1996) who used a similar method but for the penumbral region only for their sample set. There is a positive correlation r = 0.58 between umbral and the penumbral fractal dimensions for the specific sunspots. Furthermore, a time series analysis was done similarly on eight images of AR 12403, from 21st August 2015 - 28th August 2015 taken from the Debrecen Photoheliographic Data (DPD). The correlation, r = 0.623 between the umbral and penumbral fractal dimensions in the time series indicating that the complexity in morphology indicated by the fractal dimension between the umbra and penumbra followed each other in time as well.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;sun1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;White Light&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>BSc. General (Major - Physics, Minors - Environmental Physics and Material Science)</title>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <link>https://Brajkumar1992.github.io/Education/bsc/</link>
            <guid>https://Brajkumar1992.github.io/Education/bsc/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;satu2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;LX 200&quot; width=&quot;300&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2011-2016   &lt;em&gt;The University of the West Indies&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;   St. Augustine&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BSc General (Major – Physics, Minors – Environmental Physics and Material Science)&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thesis Title:&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; Observational Astronomy: The Re-Installation of the Meade 16&amp;quot; LX200&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; With the growth of Astronomy in the Caribbean, Trinidad and Tobago and the University of the West Indies, it is clear that the availability of observational research at the Department of Physics, would be a valuable asset to the UWI, St. Augustine. As such, the re-installation of the Meade 16&amp;quot; LX200 at the SATU Observatory for the purpose of scientific research and teaching was commissioned. To determine the most suitable research area for the LX200, tests to determine the systems limits were completed. The image scale was determined to be 20.82 by 20.82 arc minutes. It was also noted that, while the center of the image frame appeared free of aberrations, the degree of coma increased toward the edges. A field curvature of 24.9% and a tilt of 49% at a 59 degree angle were also discovered. These limits revealed that the LX200 would be best suited for collecting photometric data. It was suggested that the telescope be upgraded to perform wide field photometric surveys by replacing the OTA and installing a corrector lens to remove aberrations as well as replacing the CCD with a new SBIG STX-16803 CCD which would increase the image scale to 42 by 42 arc minutes.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
