<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Brandon Rajkumar - BRCreations</title>
        <link>https://Brajkumar1992.github.io</link>
        <description>A outline of my professional career.</description>
        <generator>Zola</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <atom:link href="https://Brajkumar1992.github.io/categories/brcreations/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title>Personification Series</title>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <link>https://Brajkumar1992.github.io/BRCreations/personification/</link>
            <guid>https://Brajkumar1992.github.io/BRCreations/personification/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;Sun.png&quot; alt=&quot;Sun&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet &lt;strong&gt;Eliane!&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; Personification of the Sun.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eliane has Hebrew&#x2F;Greek&#x2F;Latin origins and means &amp;quot;sun&amp;quot;. Seen here screaming becuse the Sun can sometimes be fierce. Her red hair and dark lips hint at her fiery persona. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;Mercury.png&quot; alt=&quot;Mercury&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet &lt;strong&gt;Malakai!&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; Personification of Mercury.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Malakai has Hebrew origins and means &amp;quot;my messenger&amp;quot;. Seen here as a wide-eyed kid eager to pass on messages and covered in dirt from running around. The dirt also hints at Mercury&#x27;s scared surface from its many asteroid impacts. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;Venus.png&quot; alt=&quot;Venus&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet &lt;strong&gt;Adonis!&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; Personification of Venus.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adonis has Latin&#x2F;Greek origins and means &amp;quot;very handsome young man&amp;quot;. The name is also that of a young man who entices Aphrodite in some Greek myths. Seen here with a sensual look in his eyes, his dark skin and dark orange eyes hint at the hot smoldering atmosphere of Venus. Often depicted as the goddess of love, here Venus is embodied by the namesake of one of the few men the goddess wants but cannot have according to lore. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;Earth.png&quot; alt=&quot;Earth&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet &lt;strong&gt;Terra!&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; Personification of Earth.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Terra has Latin&#x2F;Greek origins and means &amp;quot;land or territory&amp;quot;. The name was also used as the Roman goddess of the Earth.Seen here with thick green hair, complex with messy curls which represents the forests and plants of the Earth. Her dark skin hints at the rich soil beneath it all while her blue lips and eyes, along with her clothes imitate the vast oceans of the Earth.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;Moon.png&quot; alt=&quot;Moon&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet &lt;strong&gt;Luna!&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; Personification of the Moon.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Luna has Latin origins and means &amp;quot;Moon&amp;quot;. Her fair complexion hints at the bright full moon while her choppy violet hair represents the bright streaks around the moon&#x27;s craters.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;Mars.png&quot; alt=&quot;Mars&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet &lt;strong&gt;Russ!&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; Personification of Mars.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While Russ has Slavic origins and means &amp;quot;Redish blonde&amp;quot; it ws choosen as a play on rusty which describes the surface of the planet. Seen here with his rich rusty colored hair which hints at the planet&#x27;s iron rich surface while the messiness of his hair are hints to the strong winds on the planet. His intense gaze and dark eyes are homage to the planet&#x27;s depiction as the god of was in Greek and Roman mythology. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;Jupiter.png&quot; alt=&quot;Jupiter&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet &lt;strong&gt;Jeevana!&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; Personification of Jupiter.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jeevana has Hindu&#x2F;Indian&#x2F;Tamil&#x2F;Telugu origins and means &amp;quot;Life or Bringer of Life&amp;quot;. Her dark skin are representive of the dark colored atmosphere of Jupiter while her deep red lips representing the storms of Jupiter. The great red spot is represented by the dot on her forehead (called a bindi - it is traditionally worn by Hindu women to indicate that they are married. However in modern times it is also worn as fashion.)&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;Saturn.png&quot; alt=&quot;Saturn&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet &lt;strong&gt;Mira!&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; Personification of Saturn.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mira has varios origins and meetings. Here it was inspired by the Latin and Arabic origins which mean wonderful and princess respectively. Seen here with a head wrap which mimics the colors of Saturn&#x27;s surface along with her dark skin, lips and eyes. The giant hoop earrings she wears is a hint to the rings that surround Saturn.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;Uranus.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Uranus&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet &lt;strong&gt;William!&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; Personification of Uranus.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;William has Germanic origins and means &amp;quot;Resolute Protector&amp;quot;. However, the name was chosen in honor of the person who discovered the planet, Sir Willian Herchel. Seen here sporting a very disapproving look, William is tired of all the butt jokes. His aqua marine hair and beard are hints to the color of Uranus. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;Neptune.png&quot; alt=&quot;Neptune&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet &lt;strong&gt;Kailani!&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; Personification of Neptune.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kailani has Hawaiian origins and means &amp;quot;Sky and Sea&amp;quot;. Seen here with blue lips and hair which mimics the planet&#x27;s color while her messy hair hints at the strong winds of Neptune&#x27;s atmosphere. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;Pluto.png&quot; alt=&quot;Pluto&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet &lt;strong&gt;Persephone!&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; Personification of Pluto.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Persephone has pre-Greek origins and was the goddess of vegetation in Greek mythology. Here, my personification of Pluto embodies her name sake. Usually, the mythology of Persephone is that she was kidnapped and dragged by Hades (Pluto), god of the underworld into his domain. She is allowed to visit her moder for parts of the year and this is why we have seasons. However, in this depiction, Persephone was not kidnapped but  willing participant. Her fair skin and blonde hair shows her as the embodiment of spring and her ties to growth, harvest and beauty. As she accepts death and travels to the underworld with her lover, she dawns black lipstick and earrings. Her crown is made of boney claws and she adopts a stone cold glare knowing the power she has over her husband and his domain. However, her origins aren&#x27;t lost and even in her acceptance of the underworld, it shines through as shown by the dark but vivid purple flowers which adore her crown and hair sticks. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
